[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1 x 1 =",
        "answers": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "1 x 2 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "1 x 3 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "1 x 4 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "1 x 5 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "2 x 2 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "2 x 3 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            8
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 6,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "2 x 4 =",
        "answers": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            8
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 8,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "2 x 5 =",
        "answers": [
            6,
            8,
            10,
            12
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 10,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "3 x 3 =",
        "answers": [
            5,
            7,
            9,
            11
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 9,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "3 x 4 =",
        "answers": [
            12,
            15,
            18,
            21
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 12,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "3 x 5 =",
        "answers": [
            12,
            15,
            18,
            21
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 15,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "4 x 4 =",
        "answers": [
            12,
            14,
            16,
            18
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 16,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "4 x 5 =",
        "answers": [
            15,
            20,
            24,
            25
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 20,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "5 x 5 =",
        "answers": [
            20,
            25,
            30,
            35
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 25,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "6 x 6",
        "answers": [
            12,
            24,
            36,
            42
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 36,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "7 x 7",
        "answers": [
            14,
            36,
            42,
            49
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 49,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "6 x 7",
        "answers": [
            42,
            48,
            49,
            56
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 42,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "7 x 8",
        "answers": [
            42,
            49,
            56,
            64
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 56,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "8 x 8",
        "answers": [
            56,
            63,
            64,
            72
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 64,
        "clicked": false
    }
]